https://amfex.net/privacy-statement/

Country Specific Product Compliance
DATING • LABELING • WAREHOUSE • CONSOLIDATION
Home
Services
International Formatting of Production & Expiration Dating (P&E)
Company History
We’ve Gone Green!
Contact
× Home
Services
International Formatting of Production & Expiration Dating (P&E)
Company History
We’ve Gone Green!
Contact
Privacy Statement
Internet Privacy Policy At American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX, we understand that privacy is an important issue for visitors to the American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX Web site (www.amfex.net). Specifically, web users are concerned about what information is being collected, how it’s being collected and how it is being used. The following information is designed to help you understand AMFEX’s Internet Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and UseAmerican Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX gathers information about web site visitors to improve the caliber of online information and services offered. There are two forms of data that AMFEX collects: site visitor ship data and personal information voluntarily provided to us by site visitors.
Site Visitor Ship DataAmerican Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX routinely gathers data on web site activity, such as how many people visit the site, the pages they visit, where they come from, how long they stay, etc.Site visitor ship data is…
collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no personal information is associated with this data.
gathered through the use of web server logs and cookies. A web server log is a file where web site activity is stored. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site sends to a visitor’s computer, which is stored on his or her hard drive. American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX uses cookies to track repeat visits to its web site. Although American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX assigns a cookie to a visitor’s computer, the company does not know who that visitor is unless that person specifically tells us.
Personal InformationAmerican Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX collects personal information from site visitors, such as a visitor’s name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc.Personal information is…
collected only when site visitors voluntarily provide it.
collected through our mail forms. Occasionally, we will also collect personal information through voluntary online surveys.
forwarded to the American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX agent that is equipped to handle the site visitor’s request or feedback.
In reviewing American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX's Internet Privacy Policy, please keep in mind that it applies to U.S. customers and web site visitors only. If you have any questions about American Foods Export Service, Inc. / AMFEX's Internet Privacy Policy, you may contact us via Email. For details, please refer to "Contact".
